Guide to the Stanford Club of Palo Alto Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Club of Palo Alto records
1943-1998
SC0757
Stanford Club of Palo Alto (Calif.).
6.25 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Alumni Activities; Stanford alumni; Students--Societies, etc.; Universities and colleges--Alumni
Collection Contents
- Records, 1943-1998; Accession ARCH-2005-157
  - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1984 Jan-1985 Oct (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1990 Sep-1991 June (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - (Not labeled) Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1993 Apr-1996 Mar (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - (Not labeled) Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1989 Sep-1994 Mar (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, Circa 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - (Loose sheets) Images of flower bed in perpetuity by the Stanford Alumni Club of Palo Alto, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1993 Summer Fellowship, 2/3/1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - (Not labeled) Misc. Stanford Club documents, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - (Not labeled) Stanford Alumni Club presidents, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Golden Gala Invitation, 10/17/1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - (Flyer) Winning one for the Gipper: Speech Writing in the Reagan White House, 2/20/1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - (Flyer) Annual Garden Party, 6/26/1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1989 Aug-1990 Aug (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - (Not labeled) Scrap book Stanford Club of Palo Alto, Circa 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - (Not labeled) Scrap book Stanford Club of Palo Alto, Circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - (Not labeled) Scrap book Stanford Club of Palo Alto, Circa 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1992 June-1992 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - (Image) Rodin Flower Garden, 6/5/1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1986 Feb-1989 June (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, 1993 Jan-1993 Dec (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - (Not labeled) Empty Folder, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - (Images) Pictures of speakers and flowers, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Presidents - 1946-1966, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - (Images) Presidents #4-9, 1943-1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Summer Fellowship Awards, 1990, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Awards - 1951-1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Awards - 1969-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "HISTORY" "RODIN GARDEN Flower Beds", Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Albert Wilson '27 - Flower bed in perpetuity, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Agricultural tour II - Ostriches and horses, Morgan Hill, April 1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Harris Ranch tour - Highway 5, near Coalinga, November 1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Hoffman Luau, August 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hoover Pavilion - US/Russian exhibit 1900-1930, 4/23/1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Tour of Treasure Island, 5/22/1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Garden Party at Stanford University, 6/26/1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - (Sign) August 27 - open (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Monterey, Hopkins Marine Laboratory Aquarium, 9/25/1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "What Price Clean Air?", 10/29/1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Big Game at Stanford, 11/20/1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Photo album - Annual Garden Party, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Photo album - Stanford Club of Palo Alto, Aug 1991-Nov 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - News article -- George Paddleford, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Records, 1974-1989; Accession ARCH-2015-029